Contact

daffrn@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/daphny-peneza-msn-rn-cnor-cssm-tncc-b46303152 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing

Nursing Education

Perioperative Nursing

Languages

English (Full Professional)

Hiligaynon (Native or Bilingual)

Cebuano (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Basic Life Support (BLS) Instructor TNCC

Certified Surgical Services Manager (CSSM)

Certificate of Mastery Surgical Services Education

Certified PeriOperative Nurse (CNOR)

Honors-Awards

Cum Laude

AORN Promising Professional Achievement Award 2018

2018 Nursing Excellence Pillar Awards: Nurse as Innovator

PNA Metropolitan Houston's Outstanding Filipino Nurse 2018

2017 Nursing Excellence Pillar Awards: Nurse as Educator Nominee

Daphny Peneza MSN, RN, CNOR, CSSM, TNCC

RN IV / Neurological Practice Specialist - Education at Memorial Hermann Hospital Texas Medical Center

Houston, Texas

Summary

She completed her Bachelors and Masters Degree in Nursing in Ateneo de Davao University, Philippines where she was a nursing professor before migrating to Canada and USA. She was the first graduate of the Mischer Neuroscience Institute Neurosurgical Nursing Orientation Program in 2014. Last 2015 she received a Standing Ovation Award for ensuring optimal learning experiences for new employees. She is currently her institution's Nurse Mentoring Program Education Chair, Periop101 instructor, and CNOR Coach.

Daphny is a dedicated lifelong learner and believes that through learning from each other's potential and sharing our inner gifts we will all thrive towards a better perioperative nursing practice.

Experience

Memorial Hermann Health System 6 years 8 months

RN IV / Neurological Practice Specialist - Education March 2015 - Present (5 years 3 months)

Texas Medical Center

RN III / Operating Room Staff Nurse October 2013 - March 2015 (1 year 6 months)

Texas Medical Center

Bayshore HealthCare Staff Nurse / PSW October 2011 - September 2013 (2 years)

Toronto, Ontario, Canada

Ateneo de Davao University Clinical Instructor / Faculty College of Nursing May 2008 - March 2011 (2 years 11 months)

Region XI - Davao, Philippines

Notre Dame of Tacurong College Clinical Instructor / Faculty College of Nursing June 2006 - March 2008 (1 year 10 months) Tacurong, Philippines

Education

Ateneo de Davao University

Masters of Science in Nursing, Nursing Management · (2007 - 2009)

Ateneo de Davao University

Bachelors of Science in Nursing · (2001 - 2005)